

# 0

Fraccionamiento Loma Real Puebla. CP. 72100



Cel.22232342



correo@gmail.com

# Marco Antonio Ríos Sandoval

## **Profile**

Passionate and effective English teacher with experience helping students to improve their English Language speaking, reading comprehension and writing both online and in-person. Equipped with top-notch administrative skills and a solid background in tech. Systematic and well-organized with strong attention to detail. Proficient communication skills.

# **Work Experience**

February 2021 - January 2022

English Language Teacher at BALAM language school.

January 2020 - March 2020

English Language Teacher at Escuela Primaria Amado Nervo

#### October 2019

Researcher and Presenter at XV Foro de Estudios en Lenguas Internacional at Universidad de Quintana Roo

# January 2019 - April 2019

English Language Teacher at Centro de Investigación y Estudios Universitarios para el Desarrollo (CIEUD)

#### August 2019 - November 2019

English Language Teacher at Instituto Gaby Brimmer

# **Education**

## Benemérita Autónoma de Puebla. 2015-2021

Licenciatura en la Enseñanza del Inglés / English Language Teaching

Front-End Web Developer Student 2022- Present-Day

# **Highlights**

- Communication and Teamwork.
- Highly organized.
- Friendly and welcoming.
- Creative thinking.
- Computer skills
- Front-end web development skills.
- Writing Skills in Spanish and English.

# Languages

English B2 German A2 Spanish Native



